I did the the low carb diet. I'm in week
12, y'all. Week 12 is different.
>> [laughter]
>> Cuz I've lost some weight. And also, I
want to murder my family.
>> [laughter]
>> Turns out, carbohydrates is what's
holding civilization together. In case
you're wondering what was doing it.
People in Wisconsin think they don't
have an accent. And they think my accent
is adorable. So, she was like, "Your
accent is precious."
"Where are you from?" I said, "I'm from
Tennessee." She was like, "Do you date
your sister?" That's what she said.
>> [laughter]
>> I WAS LIKE, "NO. WE broke up, all
right?"
Too far, lady.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm kidding, guys. We're still together.
You make it work, okay? [cheering] You
stay in Tennessee, all right? Focus on
the family. That's what we say.
I like that no matter where you're from,
I've noticed this, no matter where
you're from, there's an area more
backwards than you that you can point
to. Have you noticed that? It's like a
coping skill.
Tennessee, we need it, okay? We're near
the bottom in education. We're like,
"Yeah, we have our bad, but what about
those slack-jawed yokels in Alabama?"
Good grief.
They're the worst. Alabama's like,
"Yeah, but come on, Mississippi. They
can barely read." [laughter] Mississippi
Mississippi's like, "Yeah, but
Paraguay."
So, that's
>> [laughter]
>> I love to travel, it's my favorite part.
I was just in Iowa for the first time a
couple months ago. Have you ever Have
you ever been to Iowa? Have you ever
been? Guys, if you get a chance You get
a chance to go to Iowa, go ahead and
skip it. Here's the deal.
Save you a trip. I'm only judging it by
the weirdest thing I saw there. I was on
a tour bus with another comedian, we're
driving along. Just corn everywhere.
Then we see a funeral home. The funeral
home sign said this, "Now offering
double-decker grave plots."
I was like, "You pull this bus over
right now."
>> [laughter]
>> I got questions.
We get out, the guy was digging the
hole. I go, "Perfect. I'll ask you, what
do you mean double-decker?" He goes,
"Well, we go 10 ft down instead of just
6, we go 10, you know. Then we put the
first person in, you know, then we put 4
ft of dirt,
>> [laughter]
>> and then I guess they wait.
And I want to be there when that second
person goes in, you know, so I'm going
to be like, "King me." You know what I'm
saying? I just need
>> [laughter]
>> You can move freely after that. That's
your best move.
Why stop at 10 ft? Go 20 ft down, put
your whole family. Just play connect
four. Do whatever you like. It's Iowa.
I told that joke in a little Baptist
church last week. It did not go well.
This lady came down to the front after
the show. I would never have a
double-decker grave plot. So, I'm like,
"Well, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to
offend you." She's like, "I'm not
offended, but my husband's not saved,
you know. So, if I die first, then they
put him on top, then the dead in Christ
try to rise, he's blocking me." And
look, THAT'S JUST
THAT'S
>> [laughter]
>> THAT'S just science, y'all. That's
I don't know.
Something about me, uh, this year I've
lost about 50 lb. I'm pretty proud of
that. 50 lb this year.
>> [cheering]
>> Working on it.
Still wearing dark colors and untucking.
This is phase two.
>> [laughter]
>> I did the, uh, the low-carb diet. Did
you ever do the low-carb thing? Is that
a thing or keto? It's a lot of cheese
and butter and meat. You can lose
weight. It's amazing. You just say, you
know, it's like, uh, you just stay away
from the carbs and the bread and the
starches and the happiness, all of that.
And then
you can lose weight. It sounds like
Disneyland for fat people. That first
week, they're explaining it to you.
You're like, "I can have a six-egg
omelet with bacon fried in an inch of
hog lard and lose weight? Sign me up,
slim. Hallelujah. Let's go."
>> [laughter]
>> That's week one. I'm in week 12, y'all.
Week 12's different.
Cuz I've lost some weight. And also, I
want to murder my family.
Turns out, carbohydrates is what's
holding civilization together.
In case you're wondering what was doing
it.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS WHOLE NORTH KOREA thing could be
solved with a crescent roll. I'm telling
you guys.
Kim Jong Un just needs some pancakes.
He's angry. Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> Right now, man.
Right now. I am uh one thing about
losing the weight, my snoring's gotten a
lot better. My wife's happy about that.
My snoring was getting so bad. I woke up
one day a few months ago. My wife was in
the next room. I was like, are we that
couple now? She's like, I can't it's too
loud.
I was like, do I have the apnea that
people are dying from that sleep apnea?
I go, do I have that? She goes, I don't
know what that is. I said, do I stop
breathing in the middle of the night?
She said, NO, I WISH.
>> [laughter]
>> I'D SAY WHAT?
Snoring's bad though. Even worse than
the snoring though, y'all, I have what's
called a night terror. Does anybody know
what night terror is? Does anybody have
that? That's not cool. I'm like seeing
stuff in the room.
You know, you think the nightmare's
over, but oh no, it's going on.
I'm punching and strangling and it's my
wife. It's bad news, y'all. It's no
good.
>> [laughter]
>> I know. And she does this, maybe some of
you ladies do this, you hang your outfit
on the door for the next day. You need
to stop doing that.
You're scaring people.
I wake up, it's like shirt, skirt, shoes
in the shape of a person.
I said, you need to stop. She said,
there's nothing on top, you I
said, which one is scarier to you, okay?
A stranger in my room at night or a
stranger in my room at night with no
head wearing my wife's clothes?
It's terrifying.
>> [laughter]
>> She started taking this stuff at night,
y'all, to sleep called ZzzQuil. Have
y'all seen this? ZzzQuil liquid from the
makers of NyQuil. Well,
cuz what? NyQuil isn't already 80 proof?
What are we doing?
Here's the commercial if you've never
seen it before. Hey, let's say you're
not sick at all.
>> [laughter]
>> But you just want to lay down for a
long, long time.
>> [laughter]
>> ZzzQuil. I was like, sweetie, call it
what it is, all right? Booze and snooze.
That's what it is.
Teetotaler, get out of here.
She's cool though, man. I'm trying to
learn to get better gifts, you know,
anniversaries uh just passed and I
noticed this Facebook and these social
media sites, they know our special days.
They start sending you ads. Have you
seen these targeted ads? The week of my
anniversary I got this one, maybe you've
seen it. For $59 you can name a star
after a loved one. Y'all see this? Name
a star for $59. I was like, yeah, or for
$0
I can just tell her I did.
>> [laughter]
>> You got an inkjet printer, you can make
up all kind of certificates. That's what
I found out.
I got Christmas taken care of.
You see that one that says Alpha
Centauri? That one's Uncle Jimmy now.
>> [laughter]
>> I love you.
One thing I'm trying to get better at
for real, be more present in our in my
marriage and that means like cell
phone's got to go, man. It's too it's
too controlling. I was in the bathroom
the other day doing my business.
Suddenly I realized I ain't got my cell
phone with me.
Y'all have that panic attack yet?
>> [laughter]
>> I WAS LIKE, WHAT AM I GOING TO DO NOW?
I WAS GRABBING ANY READING MATERIAL,
shampoo bottle, conditioner bottle,
whatever.
I was playing Tetris with the floor
tiles.
And then I grabbed the Q-tip box.
Anybody ever read the Q-tip box? Don't
do it. It'll shake you to your very
core.
>> [laughter]
>> You read that box, you realize I've been
cleaning my ears wrong for decades.
Here's what it says if you've never read
it before. The Q-tip box SAYS THIS, DO
NOT INSERT Q-TIP INTO EAR CANAL.
>> [laughter]
>> I WAS LIKE, PARDON ME?
NO, I've been cleaning my ears for 30
years and by that I mean I stick a Q-tip
all the way into my ear until I touch
what I can only imagine IS MY BRAIN.
AND THEN I TWIST IT TILL I GO
CROSS-EYED.
And I pull it out and pray there's NOT
BLOOD. THAT'S HOW YOU USE A Q-TIP WHERE
I COME FROM.
That's right.
>> [applause]
>> HERE WE GO. THIS IS A FUN JOB. I GREW UP
I NEVER KNEW I'd be a comedian. I grew
up a pretty awkward kid. I was painfully
shy. And the people always want to know
what the W is about. What's Johnny W?
It's short for my last name. I just
shortened it, make it easier for
everybody. I have a hard to pronounce
last name, so I just shortened it down,
make it easier. My last name is Baxter.
And uh
No, my last name is Weddington, which
seems easy, Weddington, but I get
Washington and Wellington and
Liechtenstein. That's a weird one. The
worst was third grade. I was in a new
school. Anybody have a hard to pronounce
last name here? You know my pain. If the
teacher gets it wrong calling roll,
you're going to get mocked the whole
year. She gets to the W's I'm sending
her telepathic messages, please get it
right. I can't deal. Weddington,
Weddington. She's like, all right,
Walker? Okay. Watson? Okay.
WEIGHT-A-TON?
>> [laughter]
>> WEIGHT-A-TON IN THE BACK, CAN I JUST
head home now and develop an eating
disorder? Thanks so much.
You're the greatest.
>> [laughter]
>> Was a chubby kid in middle school for
sure. Had asthma. You have asthma here
tonight? Hold your inhalers high. Don't
be ashamed.
I love the asthma. It was great, man.
That little asthma note from my doctor,
that was my get out of gym free card,
that's what that was. Just hand it over,
there you go, that's your copy. Okay,
it's laminated. Yeah, I got lots more.
I'm going to have a seat. Oh, we're
climbing the big rope today? I don't
think so.
>> [laughter]
>> I will not be getting friction burns on
my crotch. I'm going to have a seat
and wheeze to myself.
That was eighth grade. Then ninth grade
came, suddenly it was the high school PE
teacher. He wasn't having it. What is
this? Asthma? I can cure asthma.
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, you can what?
His cure for asthma, y'all, he made me
run uh what's called suicides. Do you
guys know what that is? Suicides? It's a
horrifying series of wind sprints. They
call it suici- I don't know who named
that, but let me tell you something. If
you make a little fat kid run back and
forth until he dies, that is homicide.
THAT IS NOT
THEY WILL PROSECUTE YOU. PRETTY SURE.
PRETTY PRETTY SURE.
BUT THAT WASN'T EVEN THE WORST DAY IN
GYM CLASS. By far the worst day was the
first gym class of 10th grade. That was
the day of the President's Physical
Fitness Challenge.
Do they do that here?
You got to stop. It's like the Hunger
Games.
>> [laughter]
>> He'd line us up. EVERYBODY TAKE A
MINUTE, GET A BUDDY. WE'RE GOING to time
each other. Everybody take a minute, get
yourself a buddy. I was like, I don't
need a minute. I don't have a buddy,
okay? I'm the shyest kid here. I look
up, everybody's got a buddy but me. I'm
mortified. I look at the end of the
bleachers, there's a girl sitting by
herself. I don't even know her. Is she
even in my class? But it doesn't matter
because they're not going to put a girl
with me. They did.
Come on down here, Sally. It's fine,
you'll be with Johnny. Come on. Now, you
going to time Johnny, okay? He going to
do push-ups for a minute, time him,
count them. Jumping jacks, you going to
count them, time him, you know. Then
you're going to hold his feet.
>> [laughter]
>> And he going to do sit-ups for a minute.
Yeah, that turned pretty quickly into a
game of how many times can Johnny fart
into the face of a stranger
before she begins to cry?
And the answer is 17. 17 times
uh is the number of times.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> I LIKE TO BE A KID UH OTHER THAN THAT
STORY. UH
I LIKE to be a kid growing up, man. Fun
stuff at church. Now, kids have all the
cool stuff at church, man. Trunk or
Treat. Anybody ever heard of that? Trunk
or Treat? I didn't know what this was.
My church did it, I was so excited, man.
Reach our community, whatever. It was
awesome watching my pastor explain it to
the older people the week before. He
gets on the mic, "Now, we know we don't
live in the same time we grew up in. We
can't be out there knocking on strange
people's doors. It's not safe. What
we're going to do
>> [laughter]
>> is going to get all the automobiles in
the parking lot
in the dark
and decorate them. We're going to teach
kids that car trunks may be full of
delicious candy. Hallelujah!
Where
Where'd everybody go?
>> [laughter]
>> My wife and I we don't have kids. That's
something about us. We have been praying
about it. All the people in my church
have been adopting. We're like, maybe
that's for us. We're and we just filed
all the process. We're going to be
adopting this year. That's pretty cool.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very [applause and cheering]
much. Excited. Very exciting.
We are adopting a highway and it's going
to be great.
>> [laughter]
>> I like giving back. I'm
We have one son, Miles. He's very tall.
>> [laughter]
>> It's hard to know if you're ready to be
a parent. I have such respect for
parents. I really do, man. And I'm an
uncle like nobody claps when you say
you're an uncle and they shouldn't.
There's no responsibility as an uncle.
You know, my little nephew Josh gets
dropped off, you know, a couple times a
month. My brother's like, "Oh, we need a
date night. Please watch him for a few
hours." Sure, man. He's just five, you
know, but I only have two rules as an
uncle. Don't be creepy. Keep him alive.
That is it.
>> [laughter]
>> That second one's hard, man. He's
mischievous. Anybody have a mischievous
child? You know what I'm talking about?
Here's how you can tell. Okay. If your
child smiles and it causes strangers to
be like, "Well, he is precious."
But when you see that same smile, you're
like, "Oh, no."
He has put the cat in the dryer again.
That's Josh. He's getting into stuff all
the time. The other day he's in the yard
playing with the neighbor kids. I'm
watching him, you know, like a good
uncle from the second story window.
>> [laughter]
>> You know, having some ZzzQuil. I look
down.
He's gone into my tool shed, brings back
a can of gold spray paint. I'm like,
"Oh, boy, here we go." But it's got the
child safe lid on it. I'm feeling fine.
Then one of his friends goes into his
dad's tool shed, brings back a hammer.
I see him motion to Josh, "Hit it with
this." You know, now if I'm a parent, I
run down there, put a stop to that
immediately. But I'm an uncle.
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, "Let's see what happens."
Y'all, he hit that can. He was instantly
gold. It's amazing how fast a person can
become gold.
He was so shiny. He comes in all this
stuff. I'm supposed to comfort him, you
know. I'm like, "Get up here, buddy.
You're okay."
I would like to thank the academy.
>> Trying to eat better on the road. It's
one thing about me, man. People want to
make you food sometimes, you know, you
get you're a guest in their home on the
road as a comic. That's interesting.
This one guy wanted to make me a
lobster. I was like, "Well, I've had
lobster restaurants. I know the whole
thing. You pick it in the tank and they
go back. You don't know what happens,
but you know, you know it was alive
then, you know?" It's different, man.
This dude was 5 ft from me in the
kitchen. I heard the sound of the
lobster going down into the pot.
This whistling screaming sound came out.
I was like, "I'm out of here."
He comes out all defensive. "Johnny,
settle down. First of all, that's not a
scream. That's just a physiological
reaction. That's air escaping. Air is
escaping." I said, "THAT'S WHAT A SCREAM
IS."
>> [laughter]
>> WE'RE WEIRD ABOUT FOOD. IT DEPENDS ON IF
THE ANIMAL'S CUTE. That's our rule, you
know? Like I'll prove it to you. We
change the name of the meat the cuter
the animal gets. Have you noticed that?
That's a weird coping mechanism. Like
chicken meat's just chicken. Fish meat's
just fish. Why? They're ugly and
beady-eyed. Kick them in the face. We
don't care.
>> [laughter]
>> We get to cows and something happens.
We're like, "Cows are cute. Look at
them." Beef. This one's beef now. It's
what's for dinner.
This isn't deer. Venison. Enjoy that.
Venison. Made up that word for you.
This isn't raccoon. This isn't a McRib.
WE CHANGE THE NAMES.
SOME OF Y'ALL LIKE, "IS THAT TRUE?"
>> [laughter]
>> WE DON'T KNOW. This is true. University
of Texas a couple of years ago, one of
the chemistry majors uh did a did a
study on all the chemicals in some of
the fast food, right? It made national
news because she found an ingredient in
McRibs also used to make exercise mats.
That's true. That's so gross. And if
you're in here tonight and you eat
McRibs, you're probably like, "What
>> [laughter]
>> is an exercise mat?"
IT'S A MOVING THING.
>> [cheering]
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> PLAY A LITTLE MUSIC FOR YOU.
WELL, THIS IS FUN, MAN. WELL, I got
married very young. I know uh
did anybody else here get married very
young in life? I was nine, my wife was
six. Anybody beat that? Uh
Tennessee's different.
No, I was 21, my wife had just turned
19. There's an energy though, man, if
you're married young. I heard it, saw a
couple of hands go, but man, I'm telling
you, like there's an energy to being
married young. It's like, "We're going
to live on love. It's us against the
world." It's super dumb. And so,
>> [laughter]
>> this is a song I wrote about that. It's
a song I wrote about living on love.
>> [music]
>> Baby, we got all we need to [music]
survive.
Cuz we got each other and we're doing
just fine. So, take my hand and walk
through the night.
Cuz we got enough to last the rest of
our lives
as long as we die by Tuesday.
And so,
>> [cheering and applause]
>> thanks.
Congratulations and good luck. Um
I love doing comedy in the clubs and
events like this are so fun, man. I do a
lot of corporate events, too. Companies
will bring me in, do big parties and
stuff. Sometimes you never know what
you're going to get with a corporate
event. I did a hunting and fishing expo
in Fort Smith, Arkansas, last month, and
I don't recommend it.
I walk out with 500 people in the dark,
head-to-toe camouflage, all of them
camouflage.
I didn't know what to do.
I was like, "Almost didn't see you
there." Nothing. I got nothing from
these people.
And
it wasn't a cool stage either, like this
with a cool curtain stuff. It was like
sheet metal screwed to the wall, and
then deer and elk heads screwed to the
sheet metal, just staring at me the
whole time. They had a stuffed turkey, a
wild turkey, at the mic stand, just
I'm not supposed to acknowledge this
turkey, just tell my jokes like it's not
there. I felt like that turkey story
needed to be told.
So, I wrote a song for those guys that
night. I thought I'd play it for y'all
here. Uh this is my turkey song, and I
hope you enjoy it, but I'm really not
counting on it.
Mhm.
Yeah.
AH!
>> [screaming]
>> HE'S GOT A GUN! THE NEXT SONG I WANT TO
DO
THERE'S ANOTHER VERSE, WE DON'T HAVE
TIME. UH
>> [laughter]
>> I KNOW IT'S COUNTRY music starting to
get into my life now. And you live in
Nashville long enough, you're just
inundated with country. I didn't really
grow up on it, but now, man, it's in my
soul. And this is a song I'm working on
with my wife. It's our 25th year
anniversary coming up, and so I thought
I'd play it for y'all. You can tell me
if I'm on the right track.
They say that feelings fade away just
like the [music] morning dew, but honey,
they don't understand the way I care for
you.
And even in our golden years, we'll
never call it quits. When we're old and
wearing diapers, wearing
Depends with benefits.
That's all I have so far, and um
thank you. That one's going to be called
I won't let you change me. It's brand
new. And so
it's new.
Thank you.
>> [applause]
>> It's new.
I got
I like country though, it's very
sincere, country music. You're wearing
your heart on your sleeve. You say what
you mean, mean what you say, you know?
You know, you're learning from the older
generation in these country songs.
They're passing down wisdom. And they
say, you go to the fishing hole with
papa, he teaches you a life lesson.
Beautiful.
But I didn't really have that kind of
relationship with my grandparents. They
were kind of creepy, kooky people.
I don't know if they could relate. This
is as far as I've gotten on my family
song. It goes, These days we're in a
hurry.
No one takes the time to listen. If we
ever stopped and looked around, we'd see
what we've been missing. Like Saturdays
at grandma's, the whole family gathered
round.
>> [music]
>> We loved to hear those stories as we sat
there on the ground. She'd tell us about
the good old days, and before she was
through, she'd offer up some free
advice, and most of it rang true. She
[music] said, Try your best, hold your
head up high, win or lose.
And don't judge a man until you've
walked a mile in his shoes. And you have
to wear this tin foil hat or the
government will read your thoughts.
>> [laughter]
>> That's when we realized that Nana might
be crazy. I got to finish [laughter]
that one.
>> [cheering]
>> Thank you. You guys
are so sweet.
I like country, I do. Give me 70s
country though. This new stuff, whatever
man. 70s, give me Merle Haggard, give me
Johnny Cash, give me some Dolly. Hank
Williams, that's country. You know what
I mean? This new stuff, if you love new
country, that's fine. To me it's just
dudes wearing girls jeans writing love
songs for their truck. It's not cool.
They're just stringing cliches together
over a beat calling it country. It
ain't. You turn on new country radio on
your way home tonight, you hear a song
like this.
>> [music]
>> She never heard the word impossible.
And she ain't familiar with regret.
>> [music]
>> She don't know the meaning of many words
at all. She's stupid.
That's offensive.
>> [laughter]
>> Well, I grew up a very random child. I
was always just saying random things,
random thoughts coming to my head. I was
always Anybody like that? You have a
random child in your family? And maybe
if you If you don't then you're the one.
It's a
I was always called like an old soul.
Anybody ever called an old soul? In your
family? That means you're a weirdo.
That's what that is. That's code
language.
I was always the random kid, man. I had
random And I still have random thoughts
coming to my head today. Have no place
in my show, you know? Or society. And so
So what I do with those, I put them with
music and I'll leave you with this. This
is something I call the joke medley and
we'll see how it goes.
>> [music]
>> On Easter Sunday
I like to take my offering and put it in
a tiny plastic egg. Make the usher
search the room for it.
Some of y'all are like, "I'm doing that
next year. That's happening."
Your dermatology conferences have
breakout sessions?
I think the slogan for Imodium A-D
should be
do YOURSELF A SOLID.
>> [applause and cheering]
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S A SLOGAN. I
APOLOGIZE.
>> [laughter]
>> AS A TEENAGER, I was really awkward
around girls.
I wasn't someone you would call someone
you would call.
I hate when somebody uses the phrase,
"That's not really my cup of tea."
Because I realize I've just poisoned the
wrong person.
So, my dad was a conjoined twin.
>> [laughter]
>> That's not the joke, man.
>> You got a lot of nerve.
>> [laughter]
>> So, my dad was a conjoined twin.
We used to refer to his brother as my
uncle on my father's side.
It's all right, guys. Settle down. It's
fine.
They were surgically separated.
[laughter]
Now, he's my uncle once removed.
It's kind of a joke, man. Thank you very
much. THANK YOU, GUYS.
TREMENDOUS.
>> [cheering]
>> THANK YOU VERY
>> [applause]
>> I'LL LEAVE YOU WITH THIS. PEOPLE ALWAYS
WANT TO KNOW, "WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE
THING ABOUT UH being a comedian?" I love
the rental car. It's a weird thing. I I
the rental car, man. And my favorite
thing about the rental car is the radio.
I leave it on the presets. I want to
hear what songs are going on in the
radio stations in the towns I'm in. Hear
my dumb phone songs for the thousandth
time. So, I pump up the radio on the
presets. I was driving through today.
It's freezing cold. I I didn't care
because I heard a song I never heard
before. I was like, "This is my jam."
I rolled down the windows at the traffic
light, pumped up the jam.
And it was a radio commercial. Does that
ever happen to anybody else? You just
feel manipulated and sad, you know?
It always starts off great and it was
like,
>> [music]
>> "I want I need I want I need." I was
like, "Yes, do it."
And it was like, "Two all-beef patties,
special [music] sauce, lettuce, cheese,
pickles, onions on a sesame seed bun."
DANG IT.
>> [applause]
>> AND NOW I'M STARVING.
AND THIS IS WHERE advertising is headed.
We got to know that. We're the TiVo
generation. We're the DVR people. We're
fast-forwarding through the commercials
at home, right? I got a DVR at home.
It's full of shows I never get a chance
to watch. I'm always traveling, you
know? They're piling up on there. I love
that show Hoarders, but I can't delete
them. I might need them. You don't know.
You don't know.
But these radio people are the worst.
They trick you, make it sound like a
song. You listen longer, they draw you
in, you know?
So, you may hear this one on your way
home, too.
>> Trapped in this place I know so well. My
home is like a
prison cell and it feels like I can't
breathe anymore.
She comes inside and dries my eyes and
takes my hand. We walk
[music and singing] outside and
I can breathe for the first time.
Allegra
Call your doctor, please. Allegra
For seasonal allergies, Allegra
>> [music]
>> If pollen makes you sneeze, don't be
afraid of trees. Just take two of these.
ALLEGRA
>> I'M JOHNNY DANG. GOD BLESS YOU GUYS.
THANK [cheering] YOU SO MUCH. Thank you
all.
I only have one pet peeve of being a
comedian. I love being a comedian. I
only have one pet peeve. Somebody sees
me on the post like you guys did
outside. There's always one person. It's
hard to make small talk before the show
cuz there's always one person. Hey, you
the comedian?
>> [laughter]
>> I'm like, yeah, I'm the comedian. All
right. Tell me a joke.
I'm like, give me a dollar. I don't
appreciate
>> [laughter]
>> We don't do that with anybody else.
Like, oh, you're a chef, bake me a cake
right now. Bake it.
Oh, you're a pharmacist, sell me some
drugs. Sell me drugs. Oh, you're from
Denver, sell me some drugs. SELL ME.
>> [applause]
>> ALL YOUR DRUGS.
>> [laughter]
>> WEIRD couple of years though. I tried to
let myself go but it's so hard. Did I
lose weight during the pandemic? No. But
did I use that time to get my mental
health straight? Also, no.
>> [laughter]
>> It's a mess up here, y'all.
It's bad news.
I tried that we joined a gym. We joined
Planet Fitness. Anybody Planet Fitness
people?
It's not a real gym, guys. It's $9.95 a
month. It's worth about $9.95 a month.
They're selling it to you. They're like,
hey, just so you know, I walk in and go,
hey,
every Monday, bagel Monday. Free bagels.
I'm like, okay. Well, that's a weird
selling point. Also, every Friday, pizza
Friday. You want free pizza.
I'm like, okay.
>> [laughter]
>> Then I look over there. There's a big
bowl of Tootsie Rolls at the check-in
counter. I'm not making this up.
I go, this is not a gym, okay?
This is a Golden Corral with treadmills.
That's what you have.
But I tried to go, man. It's hard. It's
intimidating. And then people are jacked
in the gym. People that just live in the
gym. There was a dude in there the other
day. He looked like he's about my age
but he looked like I would look, you
know, if I cared.
IT HURT my feelings.
He was cool. He had a jacked He had the
cool shaved head, too. I guess he was
going bald, he shaved his head. A lot of
guys do that. You need to know what kind
of head you have if you're going to try
that move, gentlemen.
You don't know till you shave that last
patch, do you? Could be square back
there. You don't know
what kind of craters you're working
with.
But this dude was ripped and I was
feeling bad about myself till he turned
around. When he had fat rolls on the
back of his neck,
>> [laughter]
>> it made me happy because
the way I see it, I may never have a
six-pack up here, but at least I ain't
got a pack of hot dogs on the back.
That's
That's my testimony. That's what that
is.
>> [laughter]
>> I started going to the gym with a buddy
during the pandemic, right? We're trying
to lose weight together and I was like,
"Man, we need to hold each other
accountable. Okay? We're always trying
to lose weight, we never do it. Just
let's do it, man." So, sure enough, 6:00
a.m. He joins Planet Fitness with me. We
start going every day 6:00 a.m. I look
across the treadmill, he's right there.
He's looking at me. We're running the
same miles. We're lifting the same
weights. We both lost 60 lb during the
pandemic. That's true. That's awesome,
right? Right?
And then, the other day Then the other
day, I see he comes in the locker room,
takes his takes off his shirt. I hadn't
seen him in a while. This dude's got
pecs and abs now.
And it made me furious.
Cuz I'm just like a little bit less
doughy. That's all I got going on. I'm
like a pasty deflated tire.
I go, "Dude, you were as heavy as me. We
had both lost 60 lb. You look like that,
I look like this. What's going on?" He
goes, "Dude, I'll give you the secret."
I go, "Please." He goes, "You got to
shave the hair on your chest
and your stomach and it creates like
shadows, you know, and it makes the
muscles pop when you shave them."
Don't do that. Don't do it, guys.
If there's middle-aged men in here
thinking to do it, results may vary. CAN
I JUST SAY THAT? BECAUSE
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR EXPERIENCE WILL
BE, but I look like a fat toddler now.
It's not cool.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> I try, man. I'm doing the best I can and
I don't know. It was cool to be off the
road a little bit, you know, there was
some things about it I hated, but it was
interesting. I got to be more plugged in
at my church in church folks here. We
got church people here in the crowd a
little bit, okay? Few church faithful.
I don't know, man. Church is weird
though. I love church, but it was a
little strange, man. You know, did y'all
have the first 5 months of the pandemic
2020 where your pastor's just preaching
to an empty room and a camera like a
hostage video? Did y'all go through that
phase? [laughter]
He's just reading a list of demands.
>> [laughter]
>> They're treating us well.
It's weird.
>> [laughter]
>> My church is weird though, man. But then
we started getting back together, it was
pretty cool June or so of 2020 start to
be kind of people kind of scared, but we
started to get and then Cracker Barrel
opened the same week. I was like, "The
earth is healing itself."
>> [laughter]
>> I was so excited. I knew we'd turned the
corner.
But then my wife's friend wants to come
out with us, you know, to lunch. Her my
name's Stacy and my wife's friend is a
vegetarian. Now, Stacy's fine. She's a
sweet lady, but she's a little pushy.
She's a little judgmental, okay? And if
you're vegetarian here today, hey, fine.
Eat whatever [clears throat] you want to
eat. But I was like, "I want to invite
her to Cracker Barrel, but what's she
going to eat at Cracker Barrel, okay?
>> [laughter]
>> They cook their green beans in hog lard.
What can she have? The box? What's left?
My wife is like, "It'll be okay." Y'all,
it wasn't okay. I'm having my Old
Timer's Breakfast hold my piece of bacon
like an American.
>> [laughter]
>> And I can feel Stacy's eyes on me the
whole meal. I finally was like, "What?"
She said, "Do you HAVE ANY IDEA
>> [laughter]
>> HOW THEY MAKE THAT?"
I SAID, "I DON'T, BUT YOU TELL THEM
THEY'RE NAILING it because [laughter]
>> [applause]
>> this is like a hug from Jesus. This is.
He's real, y'all. He's real.
>> [laughter]
>> And if you're a vegetarian here tonight,
please don't be offended. I want you to
feel welcome. Don't be offended. I mean,
I'm not afraid of you charging the stage
and attacking me. You're far too weak.
What I'm saying is like don't try it.
That's a lot of steps. You could get
woozy in there.
>> [laughter]
>> Church is a little weird, though. Some
churches put stencils on the walls. I've
noticed since you've gone to churches,
though, like put stuff on the walls.
White people do this a lot. This I blame
Chip and Joanna Gaines for this culture.
>> [laughter]
>> You walk into somebody's house, "Live,
laugh, love." on the wall. What is that?
What are you doing?
On my wall, I want live, laugh, leave.
That's what I want. Get out.
But my church I've been to a church
before. My church puts like our core
values and some scriptures on the walls.
I went to a church a few months ago and
they had the Ten Commandments on the
wall. And it wasn't just like all
together. It was like scattered
throughout the church just randomly. So
weird the placement of some of these
commandments. Like over the pastor's
office, I swear to you it said, "Thou
shalt not kill."
>> [laughter]
>> I WAS LIKE, "WHAT HAPPENED IN PASTOR'S
OFFICE? What I don't even know."
>> [laughter]
>> Good grief.
But one thing I really did enjoy, I got
to plug in at my church, you know, more.
That was kind of cool. We started
working in the nursery, y'all. Anybody
work in the nursery at your church? You
got to do it. It's the best cuz these
babies cannot rat you out if it all goes
wrong.
You come back after church, I hand you a
crying baby. It's like, "Look, maybe I
dropped him. Maybe he's a brat." Like,
you know.
>> [cheering]
>> YOU DON'T GET TO JUDGE ME. THIS IS THE
Lord's house, okay?
>> [laughter]
>> And we're a sticker church. I'll put in
stickers on the kids when you check them
in at your church. These big churches do
it. We're tagging these kids like
they're in the wild. It's weird.
Like it's a nature study. Sprinkle out
some goldfish crackers and track their
movements.
>> [laughter]
>> My pastor had to explain it to me,
Johnny, it's a security thing. It's got
the kids' name on the sticker, a code at
the bottom. Parent gets a piece of paper
with that same code. They come back
after church, you know, to claim their
child like it's a coat check or a
raffle. Wonderful.
>> [laughter]
>> And parents lose that piece of paper at
my church. I don't know what your policy
is at your church, but I don't put up
with that mess in my nursery.
You come back without that paper, I'm
like, "I'm sorry. We're keeping him,
okay?
>> [laughter]
>> He works for Jesus now, all right? YOU
KNEW THE RISKS."
BUT LIKE, "YOU KNOW ME, THAT'S MY SON. I
JUST DROPPED him off." I'm like, "Sir,
look, okay? [laughter]
Without the receipt,
the best I can do IS STORE CREDIT."
>> [laughter]
>> AND THEN I LET THEM PICK OUT A CHILD OF
EQUAL OR lesser [laughter] value. Sorry.
We give out so many redheads, y'all.
It's unbelievable.
>> [laughter]
>> I feel like that hurt some people's
feelings.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm kidding. Redheads don't have
feelings.
I can get through this.
I got a dumb dog. You ever have a dumb
dog? People don't want to admit their
dogs are dumb. My dog's dumb, though.
My dog's name is Toby. He's He hates
wheels, y'all, any wheels of any kind,
okay? He chases any spoked wheel coming
whirring by the house, like a bike or a
motorcycle or a wheelchair last week.
Thanks, Toby, appreciate it. We have to
move again. Thank you.
And this is true, and I'm not saying
this cuz I'm in Salt Lake City and in
Provo. This has really happened. Two
Mormons came by the house on their
missionary journey a few months ago. I'm
on the porch, I'm letting him go to the
bathroom. He chased them into a ditch.
>> [laughter]
>> I didn't know what to do. I was on THE
PORCH LIKE, "SORRY!
HE IS LUTHERAN!"
>> I DO LIKE GETTING TO TRAVEL. I I WENT TO
WEIRD places I felt like during the
pandemic. We said yes, I was talking
with the other comedians. We said yes to
so much stuff we should have said no to
cuz there's no shows. Someone calls you
just go, "I'm on my way." I did a
I did a home school convention in
Florida, y'all.
>> [laughter]
>> And this was like June of 2020, okay?
The pandemic is raging. Florida's like,
"What pandemic?" They're just firing
guns at it. "DO YOU HAVE ANY COVID?"
THEY DON'T KNOW.
>> [laughter]
>> But I went. I mean, I'm the sucker. I
went. I needed the work. I was like,
"Let's go." And I didn't know my my my
agent got me the job. He goes, "I told
them that you were home schooled your
last 2 years of high school." I go,
"That's true, but how did you even
know?" He goes, "It's my job to know."
>> [laughter]
>> But I go, "I'm not like today's home
school." Like one out of five families
home schools now. That's not how it was.
This was 1990s, okay? When I did it it
was like shut-ins and burn victims and
my family. That was the home school
community.
So I don't know if I relate to today's
home school, but this lady calls me so
excited. She's like, "Johnny, we're so
excited to have you. A thousand home
school families are waiting on you. Now
listen, you're one of us. You got to
write some home school jokes. These
people love to be teased." And I was
like, "Lady, I'm on it."
>> [laughter]
>> And they do not love it.
I came running out with my home school
jokes. It was all I could do to get out
of there alive.
Y'all want to hear the joke that upset
them?
I came running out. I WAS LIKE, "GUYS,
WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A
THOUSAND HOME schoolers and my dogs?"
And they were like, "What?" And I said,
"MY DOGS ARE VACCINATED."
>> [laughter]
>> THESE HOME SCHOOLERS WILL BITE YOU. THEY
will bite you.
>> [laughter]
>> But I like travel. I remember when I
started out, when you start doing comedy
it's the worst cuz you have to see like
you're trying to save money anything,
you know. You'll I stayed in more
people's houses like these club owners
are shady like hey don't we're not going
to get you a hotel. Come stay in the
guest room.
>> [laughter]
>> With your creepy family? You know?
No, it'll be fine. And you go in and I I
didn't want to say no I don't want to
lose out on my money. So you'd go and I
went to this one guy's house and there
was no bed in the guest room.
>> [laughter]
>> I was like is this a kill room? Be
honest with me.
Is this how it ends?
He comes back he's holding a duffel bag.
He goes I'll blow up this air bed.
You'll be good to go. Anybody slept on
one of these abominations?
>> [laughter]
>> It sounds like it's going to be amazing,
right? It's a bed made of air. Sounds
like you're going to be sleeping on a
cloud.
You're on this thing 5 seconds you're
like this is a pool toy. I'M ON A POOL
TOY.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR EXPERIENCE IS
ON THE air bed, but I'm 6'4" 250 lbs.
I'm a big person, okay?
>> [laughter]
>> So the air slowly leaks out of the air
bed overnight. Do you ever have that
happen? You wake up you're on the
ground. The bed is around you somewhere.
Right? You lay down on a mattress. You
wake up in an inflatable shame taco. NOT
COOL.
BUT I NEVER WAS COOL. I WAS ALWAYS LIKE
AN awkward kid, man. So uncool. And I
was painfully shy. And I remember in the
middle school it's the worst, man. These
gym class games, oh my gosh. I felt like
they were like to weed the doughy kids
like me out, you know. It was like a
Lord of the Flies in there.
Like even the names of some of the games
like RED ROVER RED ROVER. YOU SEPARATED
MY SHOULDER. YOU'RE injuring children.
You're hurting [laughter] people.
You know?
Middle school but for boys it's hard.
Girls have it hard, too. I get it. And I
always hear about this, you know. Girls
My wife always tells me like you know,
it's so hard for girls cuz your body's
developing and you're judged on your
appearance and other girls are so mean
to you and it's all that. Like I get it.
But boys have it hard, too, right? Like
Listen, when you're in middle school you
don't know anything about sex. you don't
know anything about your body, but you
have to pretend you know, cuz you want
to be a man.
What you're hoping that you're hoping
against hope that somebody in health
class will ask the question that you
want to know the answer to, right? You
desperately want to know, but you don't
want to ask. You're hoping that way you
can be like, "What a weirdo." [laughter]
All right, noted.
These people are health class heroes,
that's what they are.
They fell on the grenade for all of us.
And for me, I'll never forget it was
eighth grade, my buddy Chad.
Mr. Traywick's like got the little
pointer out and he's pointing at the
anatomy chart, you know, in health
class, and he gets to the ovaries. Chad
sheepishly raises his hand, "Mr.
Traywick,
WHERE ARE MY OVARIES?"
>> [laughter]
>> MR. TRAYWICK SAID, "SON, you don't have
ovaries." [laughter]
And a lot of us laughed, you know.
But some of US WERE LIKE,
>> [laughter]
>> "WHAT HAPPENED TO CHAD'S OVARIES?"
[laughter]
>> "And how does Mr. Traywick know?"
>> [laughter]
>> It is, man, it's hard. And that's the
thing, travel's been weird during the
pandemic. I like it, but it's just so
strange. You just do the best you can.
And I've rented so many dumb cars, you
know, and now there's a car shortage.
They're blaming COVID. What's that all
about?
Sorry, the cars have COVID. What's that?
What's happening? Why are there no cars?
You show up and like, "I've got a
reservation for a mid-size." They go,
"Well, isn't that precious."
>> [laughter]
>> We don't have any cars. And then they
just reach into a drawer and throw you
keys to whatever. Usually it's a
minivan. I get so many minivans, y'all.
And I used to make fun of these soccer
moms with your mini vans. Not anymore.
These things are awesome. They're like
spaceships.
Big old DVD screens are popping down,
buttons and readouts. I love it.
We I took a trip with my wife and this
thing had dual climate control, this van
we had. Y'all have that? I didn't know
what it was. It worked out awesome. My
wife's always freezing. She's pumping
the heat full blast on her side. So I
got to counteract her, you know, pump
the AC on my side. We made a funnel
cloud. THAT THING
MY DOG GOT STRUCK BY LIGHTNING.
PRAY FOR US, YOU KNOW.
>> [laughter]
>> BUT YOU do we rent so many dumb cars.
And then you win the rental car is a
whole thing, you know, it's a whole
process. And I've gotten good at it over
the years. I've got to rent 100 cars a
year. But you got to stop Listen, some
of you some of y'all travel for
business. You got to know this. Listen,
some things are worth the money. Stop
bargain hunting on some of this stuff
cuz you get messed over. I had to rent a
car in Austin, Texas last week and I
found out the day before. I was like,
all right, I got to quickly go. And I
went on [clears throat] like, you know,
whatever pay less, you know, quality
with a K, one of those kind of sites.
And I'm clicking around to find my car
and I clicked on one that said Chevy
Impala or similar.
>> [laughter]
>> Not similar.
I show up there's one car left in the
parking lot at Austin Airport. It was a
2014 Toyota Yaris hatchback.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah. I don't know if you've ever seen a
Yaris hatchback, but it looks like you
could pull it back on the kitchen floor
and let it go. It's that kind of car.
And I'm 6'4, 200 and 20 pounds. I'm a
big person.
So I'm looking at this guy like, I don't
know what you think you're going to do
to shoehorn me into this vehicle. Is
there a bone saw in your back pocket?
Because
he wedged me into that car, y'all. I
pulled out of that parking lot looking
like Wreck-It Ralph.
>> [laughter]
>> Sometimes they upgrade you. That's
pretty cool. And you know, you tell when
I pull in Salt Lake City they gave me an
Infiniti, y'all. What? Infiniti? What?
This thing had leather seats, heated
seats. Boom! Anybody have heated seats?
Well, I do, now.
Heated seats are awesome, y'all, if you
know you have them.
IF NOT, I PROMISE YOU, IT'S TERRIFYING.
I'M HALFWAY TO THE CLUB. I must have
bumped the button with my water bottle,
put it in the cup holder. I just feel
heat radiating through my body.
>> [laughter]
>> It took me 5 minutes to realize I wasn't
HAVING A STROKE.
>> [laughter]
>> BUT I WASN'T COOL. I WAS LIKE, YOU GET
IN TROUBLE WHEN YOU try to look cool. It
messes you up every time. We're all
going to look stupid. You're going to
look stupid. Just go with it. I'm in my
40s now. I realize it it happens all the
time. When you try to stop it, it just
comes out more.
I carry this guitar in my little gig bag
over my shoulder, and every airport in
America, at least one person will come
to me and be like, "Hey,
what you got in there?"
>> [laughter]
>> I'm like, "You seen the shape? Magic
beans? What do you think's in here?"
But I do it to y'all. I'm a dummy. I did
a a corporate event over Christmas. It
was like for a really nice Fortune 500
company. They brought me out to their
Christmas party. I was like, what is
this? It's a really nice, you know,
cocktail party-type atmosphere. And they
took me to my green room. And in the
green room was this sofa and a lamp and
a table. On the table was a menu for an
Italian restaurant, a little bistro down
the corner. They said, "You can order
anything you want. This will be your
meal for the night." I was like, "Oh,
this is awesome. I'm a big-time
comedian. A meal just for me? Well,
well, well." Then I look at the menu.
It's in all Italian.
I'm going to start freaking
[clears throat] out, y'all.
Cuz I didn't grow up like that. I'm 1/4
white trash, okay?
I don't know anything about real Italian
food. You know, like Kraft Mac and
Cheese with hot dogs cut up in it.
That's what I had. You know what I'm
saying? Chef Boy R D is my chef. Do you
understand me?
Or like on a fancy night, we might go
out to Olive Garden. What? Olive Garden?
Get out the good sweatpants. That kind
of thing.
>> [laughter]
>> You get it.
So, I didn't know. I was I'm having a
panic attack looking at this menu. I
don't want to look stupid. My brother
was there. I go, "Dude, you know any of
these words?" I go, "What's cavatappi?"
He goes, "I think that's uh corkscrew
pasta."
And I go, "Well, I thought that was
called rotini."
He goes, "Yeah, I think you're right."
>> [laughter]
>> And then I said this out loud to another
person. I said,
"Well, maybe it goes THE OTHER WAY."
>> [laughter]
>> CAN'T TAKE THAT BACK, Y'ALL. THAT'S
DONE. That's real done.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Talk about plugging into my church.
Here's one thing about my church. I
don't know if your church has small
groups. We have small groups. My My My
pastor plugged me into a small group
though that's like full of hunters, all
these hunters.
It's weird cuz I'm on the road all the
time and I don't really I'm not a gun
guy. I'm not anti-gun. Have your guns,
Utah. Do what you want to do. I don't
have a gun. I have night terrors is what
I have. So,
whatever you think about the Second
Amendment, we can at least agree I don't
need a gun. I just need to take out the
coat rack 10 times a night.
>> [laughter]
>> And I get that it puts me at a
disadvantage not having a gun. If there
was an intruder, I'd be like, "Can't we
just talk this out?"
No? Okay. Sweetie, he wants you to go
with him.
>> [laughter]
>> I'll miss you so much.
But, he puts me in this group with all
these guys who go and they have all
these stories. I feel left out, man. The
closest thing I have to a hunting story
all is I have a buddy who won't put down
his dumb phone. You heard this, man?
We're We're too addicted to our phones.
We're going 60 mph. I'm in the passenger
seat. He's on Facebook. I'm like,
"You're going to kill us." Okay. And
then he drops his phone accidentally. He
goes, "I'll get it." You'll get it?
>> [laughter]
>> I'll get it. We go down together. Who's
driving the car? No one.
And then we start to veer off the road
on the shoulder and we jump the little
divider and there's like a culvert on
I-40 in Tennessee flowing like water
flowing in a little creek and we jumped
and we're in midair and I'm like, we're
dead. And then we just this huge splash,
but we were I couldn't believe we were
okay. I knew something had like broken
our fall. Sure enough, there had been a
deer drinking from the culverts.
[laughter]
And I don't know how to say this
diplomatically, but we mashed him real
good.
>> [laughter]
>> It was like Wicked Witch of the East
coming out of the bottom of that car,
just four hooves.
And I know we teach children that
animals are innocent, but let's be real.
Okay, if you're just having a sip of
water one day and out of the sky God
drops a car on you, okay,
>> [laughter]
>> that deer was up to something. Can we at
least admit
there was sin in his life. That felt
That felt like a reckoning to me.
But I couldn't wait to go be around my
hunting buddies again. They're always
trying to get me to go hunting. I was
like, hey, guess who bagged a deer last
weekend?
He's like, OH MY GOSH, WHAT DID YOU USE?
I SAID, A COROLLA. So that's a great
>> [laughter]
>> I like a nice dark joke like that. It
lets me know what kind of sickos you
guys are. It makes me feel better.
Cuz I've learned this, there's only
three kinds of people in the world, only
three kinds. Person number one, someone
trips and falls, you ask if they're
okay, and then you laugh at them. That's
person number one.
Then there's person number two, you
laugh first and you're like, are you
okay?
Number two.
Then there's me, I'm person number
three. I trip that person to see what
kind of person you are.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm not good.
I'm going to be okay. Hey, can I play a
little music for you before we go? IS
THAT OKAY?
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> I WAS GOING TO DO IT ANYWAY.
GUYS, YOU'RE AWESOME, MAN. I love living
in Nashville. It's
country music capital. I didn't really
grow up around country music. Now it's
late in life I get into it, but I'm into
like 1970s country. I think that's the
best country. That's the best decade.
You had Hank and Waylon and Merle. These
were UGLY PEOPLE.
>> [laughter]
>> COUNTRY MUSIC YOU NEED PAIN cuz you're
drawing from pain in your life and
writing these sad songs and you need to
I'm I'm telling you ugly people GOT MORE
PAIN.
>> [laughter]
>> THEY DO.
AND THEY HAVE BETTER STORIES, you know?
If you're too pretty, you just float
through life. That's not good for a
country song, you know? Merle Haggard
looked like he walked 5 mi on his face,
y'all.
>> [laughter]
>> And these new guys, Keith Urban, he's
talented, but look, he's too pretty.
Look at him. What kind of pain has Keith
Urban experienced? Did he burn himself
with his hair straightener? No.
>> [laughter]
>> But it's weird, man. Country songs are
sad and I like those. I hear I get
nostalgic. You ever hear the saddest
songs you know, like when you break up
with somebody, like your first breakup,
your first love, you hear that song on
the radio, it sounds like they're
singing right to you. You just feel you
feel it right in your chest. Remember
that when you're in high school or
something? You're like, "Every rose does
have its thorn."
It's true.
It happened during COVID for me because
I would notice that like songs that were
like old, they felt like they could have
been written during the pandemic. They
felt very like prescient, you know? Like
they were just like predicting the
pandemic. I heard a song It's about a
10-year-old song. I heard it on the way
here in the rental car. And it's
definitely a COVID song. It goes like
this.
If I lay here
If I just lay here
Can I just lay here and just [music]
keep laying here? That guy's lazy.
I hate like question songs. You ever
hear a song It's like a question, but it
doesn't answer the question in the song.
Just leaves you hanging. Or it's like
it's like an easy question, but they
never they never figure it out. It goes
on. There's a song I heard on the radio
on the way here. It's like an oldies
station. I listen to the Carpenters.
Remember the Carpenters? Some of you are
older people here.
So, they have a song that's a question
song. It goes on for 4 minutes. That
song should have been over in 9 seconds.
It's an easy question. If you don't know
what it goes like this.
>> [music]
>> Why do birds suddenly appear
every time you [music] are near? Because
I have bread.
>> [laughter]
[cheering]
[laughter]
>> I DON'T KNOW.
MY MARRIAGE MADE IT THROUGH THE
PANDEMIC, that's pretty cool. I was home
a lot and then my wife still loves me,
that's pretty good. It's stuff like that
and uh
she puts up a lot. Y'all know I'm a
smart I'm a professional smart like
literally.
And I tell her she gets onto me like
five or six times a day I'll say
something just so sarcastic to her. And
the other day she was like, "Why do you
always do that?" And I go, "Sweetie,
I get it. I could do better.
But give me credit for what I'm holding
in. Can you imagine
the things I'm not saying right now?"
But sometimes they slip out. You know
what I'm talking Married people, you
know what I mean. Sometimes you can't
stop yourself from saying the just just
the worst stuff. We're at We're at
Hampton Inn last weekend. My wife went
out on tour with me and we're at Hampton
Inn. Hampton Inn is one of those places
where they got rid of the breakfast.
You're paying for it still but they go,
"Sorry, COVID, no breakfast. Here's your
bag with an apple and a bagel."
You throw it in the trash. That's what
they're basically saying.
>> [laughter]
>> So now the breakfast is coming back. I
feel all excited till I realize this
breakfast was never good. No, it's
awful. This rubbery bacon, these
powdered eggs, they're all watery and
weird. Those eggs at the breakfast
buffets are so bad.
My wife she's eating them though. We're
just trying to make our flight. She's
eating these runny powdered eggs and
then she looks at me and she says,
"Johnny, how do they even make powdered
eggs?"
>> [laughter]
>> And I said, "Sweetie, when two powdered
chickens love each other very much."
>> [laughter]
>> And she didn't speak to me the rest of
the day but it was worth it. I got to
tell you, that was
Well, I'll leave you with this. Uh this
is something I like to do to close the
show. It's something I call the joke
medley, just a lot of random thoughts I
put with music and uh I hope you enjoy
it, but I'm really not counting on it.
>> [music]
>> I want to host a game show where redneck
contestants answer trivia questions for
cash and prizes.
And wrong answers cost them their hair.
>> [laughter]
>> It's called mullet over.
[music]
>> I thought it was pretty cool when I was
a kid and my dad pulled my loose tooth
using the old string around the doorknob
method.
It was less cool WHEN HE TOOK OUT MY
TONSILS.
I want to find 10 people who are giving
it 110%
so that I can continue coasting at 0%.
Arizona makes me nauseous, but it's A
DRY HEAT.
I THINK books about bankruptcy should
start with chapter 11.
>> [music]
>> After seeing my doctor open a Capri Sun
pouch, I hope I never need an emergency
tracheotomy.
Allergies are really bad in Tennessee.
We're always number one in allergies.
Here's how bad it is in Tennessee. We
got people in Tennessee now buying meth
to turn it back into Sudafed.
>> [music]
>> I hate racism. Even more than that
though, I hate like pretense. I hate
just
posturing about race, you know?
Like whenever a white person doesn't
want to be accused of being racist, they
always say something dumb like, "I'm
colorblind. I don't see color."
But my grandmother was color blind and
racist.
She used to tell us kids, you can't
trust those gray people.
>> [laughter]
[music]
>> My buddy's trying to cheer me up the
other day, comes over, he's always too
cheery. He's like, "Johnny, you know it
takes twice as many muscles to frown as
it does to smile."
I said, "I know.
It's worth the extra effort."
>> [laughter]
>> My mommy always says, "A spoonful of
sugar makes the medicine go down."
It was true of EVERYTHING EXCEPT
SUPPOSITORIES.
I CALL THAT joke sweet and low.
>> [music]
>> I'm Johnny Devito. God bless you, guys.